# **ELISABET VAZQUEZ**

Los Angeles, CA | (+1) 310-254-0759 | elisabetvz.com | elisabetv.design@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/elisabetv Ready to start working in September 2022 | Available for Full-Time or Contractor Position

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

I'm an interdisciplinary creative focusing on Graphic Design, specializing in typography, brand design, layout design and art direction. I acquired a Political Science degree from UCL exploring a range of subjects, mainly focused on international relations, economics, social psychology, cognitive approaches to foreign policy, and strategic project management. My diverse background has allowed me to hone my problem-solving skills to provide effective solutions and innovative design.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **UCL** (UNIVERSITY COLLEGE LONDON)

LONDON, UK

Bachelor of Arts - Politics, Sociology and East European Studies.

SEP. 2019 - JUN. 2022

- Grade: 2:1 (i.e.: 3.7 GPA)
- Dissertation on Cognitive Approaches to Foreign Policy Analysis

**UCLA EXTENSION** 

LOS ANGELES, USA

Certificate, Design Communication Arts

Jun. 2021 - Aug. 2022

Certificate, Directing

Mar. 2022 - Aug. 2023

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# MINA BAIE (Retail Company)

LOS ANGELES, USA

Junior Graphic Designer

SEP. 2022-current • Designed Emails, GIFs for Reels, Stories and Posts. Retouched + Color Corrected Images for Web + Socials.

## JUICE HOUSE (Creative Agency)

REMOTE

Creative Intern

SEP. 2022-current

- Creative Direction, Social Planning and Management of @juicehousecreative account
- Content Creation and Ideation for Artist's Personal Brand + Socials, working with @itsduncanlaurence, @sofiavaldes, @trinsgby,

MOSAIC (NGO) LOS ANGELES, USA

Creative Team Lead

JUN. 2022-current

 Led a team of 6, art directing and creating graphics and social media content, as well as supervising a team for motion graphics, digital design, photography. Main focus: graphics, photography, social media management.

Hillsong UK (NGO)

LONDON, UK

Photographer

SEP. 2019 - MAR. 2022

Providing Photography and Photo Editing for weekly events and conferences.

### A21 UK (NGO, Human Trafficking Relief)

LONDON, UK

Social Media Manager

MAR. 2020-AUG. 2020

- Led a Creative Team of 5, to create graphics and copywriting for social media campaigns.
- Developed brand awareness in social channels through content management, strategy, planning and goal setting.

## **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

### TBN España (Studio, Film & TV)

MADRID, SPAIN

Jan. 2018-Aug. 2018

English-Spanish Translation and Subtitling of TV Episodes.

## **LANGUAGES**

English (fluent, C2); Spanish (native); French (advanced, C1).

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Photoshop | Illustrator | InDesign | CSS | HTML | After Effects | MS Office | Power Point | Research | Scheduling | Photography | Lightroom | Sketch | Social Media Management | Project Management

### **OTHER INFORMATION & CERTIFICATES**

- Confident Copywriting 6-week Short Course from UAL College of Communication (2020).
- Coded and designed my own portfolio website (elisabetvz.com) using HTML and CSS.
- 1-year Leadership Program covering subjects as critical thinking, theology, personal development (2020–2021)